A Finding Aid to the John Henry Bradley Storrs Papers, 1790-2007, bulk 1900-1956, in the Archives of American Art AAA.storjohn
Archives of American Art
- Personal Business Records, 1790; 1855-1987; Series 3; 2.9 Linear feet Boxes 7-9, 25, OV 24, 28
  - Commission Files (Box 8)
    - Church of Christ the King, Cork, Photographs, circa 1932 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Court House Elevator Doors, Saint Paul, Minnesota, 1930-1932 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Public Works of Art Project, 1931-1938 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Statue of Jeanne d'Arc, Orleans, France, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Worcester War Memorial, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Commissions and Project Documents, 1921-circa 1930s (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Contracts and Agreements, 1912-1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Ecole de la Loire Documents, 1953-1955 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Estate Records, Deville-Chabrol Family, 1861, 1894, 1895; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
  - Financial Records (Box 8)
    - Bankers Trust Company Records, 1928-1931 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1855-1868; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 28-30)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1905-1956, 1970-1975; (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 31-33)
    - Undated Bills and Receipts, circa 1855-1975 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Check Stubs, circa 1920-1938, 1955; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
    - Insurance Records, circa 1932-1933; (Not scanned) (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Ledgers, circa 1903-1927; (5 volumes) (Box 8, Folder 38-42)
    - Ledgers, 1922-1953; (2 volumes) (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Loose Pages from Ledger, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Northern Trust Company Records, 1923-1956; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
    - Stock Market Records, 1929-1932; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Tax Records, 1930-1956; (Not scanned) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Financial Documents, 1911-1957 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Chateau de Chantecaille (Box 25)
    - Auction Posters, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      Oversized materials housed in OV 28.
    - Drawings and Plans, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 25, Folder 19)
      Oversized material housed in OV 28.
    - Guest Book, 1925-1985 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - House Records, 1790 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - House Records, 1921-1965 (Box 25, Folder 22-27)
    - "Plan de la Terre de Chantecaille", undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Furniture Appraisal, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Furniture Inventory, 1950; (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
  - Leases, 1921-1932 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Notes for an Inventory, circa 1921 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Patent Documents, 1864-1865 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Plan and Plant Installation" Diagram, circa mid-1900s (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Travel Forms and Passes, 1906-1918, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Oversize A Century of Progress Exposition, Photographs, 1933; (Scanned with Box 8, F15) (Box OV 24)
  - Oversize Chantecaille Auction Posters, 1921 (Box OV 28)
    Oversized material from Box 25, Folder 18.
  - Oversize Chantecaille Drawings and Plans, circa 1920s-1950s (Box OV 28)
    Oversized material from Box 25, Folder 19.
- Diaries, 1874-1955; Series 4; 0.9 Linear feet Boxes 9-10
  This series contains 48 diaries belonging to John Storrs and a few diaries belonging to others. Most of Storrs' diaries are small pocket "engagement diaries," with records of events written under each date. Some diaries only include scattered entries and are not complete. Some also contain scattered notes and addresses. The most detailed diaries date from 1944 to 1955. Of interest are entries from his early diaries while Storrs was still a student in Chicago, his diaries from 1906-1907 while studying in Hamburg with Arthur Bock, and illustrated diary entries from 1919. Other diaries found here include one diary detailing David William Storrs' trip to Rome in 1874, one small pocket diary belonging to Marguerite Storrs, and two diaries belonging to Monique Storrs containing a few written entries.
  Diaries are arranged in chronological order.
  - John Storrs Diaries, 1898-1922; (5 folders) (Box 9, Folder 18-22)
  - John Storrs Diaries, 1923-1931; (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 23-26)
  - John Storrs Diaries, 1932-1944; (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 27-30)
  - John Storrs Diaries, 1845-1949; (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 31-34)
  - John Storrs Diaries, 1950-1955; (3 folders) (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - David William Storrs Diary, 1874 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Marguerite Storrs Diary, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Monique Storrs Diaries, 1939, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Writings, 1888-1989; Series 5; 1.1 Linear feet Boxes 10-11, 25
  This series contains writings by John Storrs and others. Writings by Storrs include his memoirs, notebooks, poetry, and writings on various subjects. Other writings are by Jessie Dismorr, Zoltan Hecht, Maurice Raynal, David William Storrs and others, and include poetry, writings about Storrs, notebooks, and miscellaneous writings.
  The series is arranged as 2 subseries:
  5.1: Writings by John Storrs, 1897-1955
  5.2: Writings by Others, 1888-1970s
  - Writings by John Storrs, 1897-1955; 5.1
    Found here are four volumes of John Storrs' memoirs as well as a typed annotated transcript of the memoirs. The first volume was written during his World War II imprisonment from 1941 to 1942, and the second after after returning home in 1942, and the third and fourth from 1946 to 1947. The memoirs briefly mention his imprisonment, but primarily detail his family history and his life from birth to 1906 when he completed his studies with Arthur Bock in Hamburg, Germany.
    Other writings include a notebook containing descriptions of his dreams, a notebook of religious poetry, thoughts, and sketches, and an additional 15 notebooks which contain notes about his artwork and art in general, lists, addresses, sketches, quotes, and poetry. Some notebooks only contain a few pages of writing. Also found is a large amount of poetry, in various draft forms, written by Storrs over a 45 year period. Other items of note are written personal accounts of his mother's death, an art class in Paris, World War II, and the death of Auguste Rodin.
    - Memoirs, vol. I, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Memoirs, vol. II, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Memoirs, vol. III, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Memoirs, vol. IV, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Transcripts of Memoirs, 1942-1947 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Notebook on Dreams, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Notebook, "To you my Lord, this book of prayers in words", 1935-1940 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Notebooks, circa 1904-1920s; (5 folders) (Box 10, Folder 14-18)
    - Notebooks, 1930-1946; (5 folders) (Box 10, Folder 19-23)
    - Notes, circa 1905-1955; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 24-25)
    - Poetry, 1910-1918; (4 folders) (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
    - Poetry, 1933-1955; (4 folders) (Box 11, Folder 5-8)
    - Poetry, Undated Draft Versions, circa 1910-1955 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Record of Letters Sent and Received, 1905-1912 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - School Assignments, 1897-1902 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - ["Night Class at an Art School?"], circa 1912 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "Death of Hannah, July 24, 1913" (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Writings about Auguste Rodin, circa 1940s (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Writings about Dreams, 1930-1947 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Writings about World War II, 1940-1946 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Writings, circa 1905-1955 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Writings by Others, 1888-1989; 5.2
    Scattered writings by others include a booklet of poetry written by Storrs' friend and fellow artist Jessie Dismorr, an open letter concerning the New-Age group by artist Zoltan Hecht, and an essay (in French) by art critic Maurice Raynal about the work of John Storrs. Also found are notebooks belonging to Storrs family members, and a handmade notebook which includes poetry written by musician Arthur Olaf Andersen, artist Richard H. Recchia, writer Paul Scott Mowrer, and others. Also contained here are various writings and notes by unidentified authors.
    - Jessie S. Dismorr, "Poems", 1918 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - William Joy, "Forward to an Address on American Art Given Before the Fortnightly Club of Chicago", 1911 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Zoltan Hecht, "An Open Letter Whom It May Concern" (Regarding the New-Age group), circa 1928 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Maurice Raynal, "Sur L'Oeuvre de John Storrs", circa 1929 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - David William Storrs, Notebook, 1915-1918 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Marguerite Storrs, "Courier" Notebook (Letters Posted), 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mary Storrs, School Notebook, 1888-1890 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Various Authors, Notebook of Poetry, 1907-1912 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Various Authors, Miscellaneous Writings, circa early-1900s-1970s (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Unidentified Author, "Dr. Zay", circa early-1900s (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified Author, Notebooks, circa late-1800s; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified Author, "A Livre le Premier", circa late-1800s; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified Author, Speech for "Inauguration de L'Exposition John Storrs, La Bibliotheque Municipale D'Orleans", circa 1949 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Notes Written by Others, circa 1950s-1989 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Printed Material, 2005; 1867-1987; Series 6; 3.6 Linear feet Boxes 11-14, 25, OV 24
  There is a large amount of printed material documenting Storrs professional and social activities, including books; art bulletins; brochures, including a brochure for a painting class taught by Storrs; invitations, announcements, and programs for art and social events; blank postcards; and published reproductions of his artwork. Also found are exhibition catalogs for individual and group exhibitions of Storrs' artwork, including a few catalogs published by the Société Anonyme, as well as catalogs for exhibitions of works by other artists. This series also includes rare magazines such as a bound volume of the first ten issues of The Liberator, a radical political magazine and successor to The Masses. Many of the magazines and books in this series are in French. News clippings include biographies and obituaries, reviews of exhibitions and commissions for public sculptures, and other news related to Storrs, his daughter Monique, and his friends. Additional clippings are found within the Scrapbooks in Series 9.
  This series has been partially scanned. Items not scanned include books, blank postcards, and other published material not directly concerning John Storrs or his career as an artist.
  This series is arranged by type of material and chronologically within each folder.
  - Advertisements of Female Hairstyles, circa 1920s (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - "Artists' Directory" (Chicago, Illinois), early 1900s (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Auction Catalog, "20th Century American Paintings and Sculpture", 1973 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Book Catalogs and Order Forms, 1927-1936; (Not scanned) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Books (Box 11)
    - Les Albums D'Art Druet: Maillol, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Anthologie De La Peinture En France De 1906 A Nos Jours by Maurice Raynal, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - L'Art by Auguste Rodin, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - L'Art Decoratif, Le Mobilier Moderne, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - The Art of Fresco Painting by R. La Montagne St. Hubert, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Chien-Mi-Lo by Oskar J. W. Hansen, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Famous Comic Recitations, 1893 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Peintres d'au jourd'hui by Gaston Diehl, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - La Peinture et La Litterature Libres (Vrille) by Evrard De Rouvre, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - The Way Beyond 'Art' by Alexander Dorner, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Brochures and Flyers, 1874, 1904-circa 1940s (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Brochure for John Storrs Painting Class, circa 1930 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Bulletins (Box 12)
    - "Bulletin of the Art Institute of Chicago", 1929-1935; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "Bulletin of the Section of Painting and Sculpture" (Treasury Department), 1935, 1937; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "The Fortnightly of Englewood", 1900-1913; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "The Print Collector's Bulletin", circa 1920s; (Not scanned) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Bulletins, 1912-1966; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
      Partially scanned.
  - Event Invitations and Announcements, circa 1904-1935, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, John Storrs Exhibitions, 1913-1924; (4 folders) (Box 12, Folder 8-11)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, John Storrs Exhibitions, 1926-1931; (5 folders) (Box 12, Folder 12-16)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, John Storrs Exhibitions, 1933-1940; (5 folders) (Box 12, Folder 17-21)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, John Storrs Exhibitions, 1948-1980; (5 folders) (Box 12, Folder 22-26)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, John Storrs Exhibitions, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Other Artists, 1908-1975; (17 folders; not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 1-17)
  - Magazines (Box 13)
    - Action, 1920-1922; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 18-20)
    - Architecture and Design, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Brush and Pencil, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Carnet, 1931; (Not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Les Feuillets D'Art, 1919; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 24-25)
    - Les Feuillets D'Art, 1919-1920; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - The Liberator, vol. 1, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - The Little Review, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Playboy, 1919 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - La Renaissance d'Orleans, 1945; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Shelter, 1932; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Truth, 1898; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The University High School Weekly, 1904-1905; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1919, 1927, 1929, 1949; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Map of New Orleans, 1867 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - News Clippings, 1907-1949; (4 folders) (Box 14, Folder 13-16)
  - News Clippings, 1950-1987; (5 folders) (Box 14, Folder 17-21)
  - News Clippings regarding Monica Storrs, 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - News Clippings, Source Images, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Postcards of Europe & U. S., early 1900s; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Postcards of France & Monaco, early 1900s; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Postcards of Italy, early 1900s; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Postcards of Works of Art, early 1900s; (3 folders; Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 26-28)
  - Postcards of Miscellaneous Subjects, early 1900s; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Posters, circa 1930s; (Oversized items housed in OV 24) (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Press Report, Fairmount Park Art Association 3rd Sculpture International, 1949; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Programs, 1904-1955; (4 folders) (Box 14, Folder 32-35)
  - Publications about Persian Art, 1934; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Published Speeches by Governor of Cyprus, 1927-1928; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Reproductions of Artwork, circa 1920 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - WPA: Federal Art Project Manual, 1935; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, circa late 1800s-1935; (Not scanned) (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 2005; circa 1976-1988 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Posters, circa 1930s; (Scanned with Box 14, F30) (Box OV 24)
- Photographs, circa 1885-1980; Series 7; 3.2 Linear feet Boxes 14-16,18, 20-22, 25, MGP 1, MGP 2, MGP 5, MGP 6
  Photographs are of John Storrs, his family, friends, various places from his travels, and his artwork. Photographs of Storrs depict him as a child, in Europe from 1905 to 1907, in his studio in both Germany and Paris, creating work for the Century of Progress Exposition, and with friends and family, including wife Marguerite. Also found are two photographs of him in art classes. Additional photographs depict Marguerite, the dancer Maud Allan, Storrs' instructor Arthur Bock, and fellow artist and model Gertrude Lambert. Other photographs of friends are mostly unidentified. Also found are photographs of the interiors of his studios and various residences.
  Three photograph albums document Storrs' time in Europe from 1905 to 1907 and include photographs of him, his sister Mary and other family members, friends, Arthur Bock in his studio, and various monuments and streetscapes from his travels. Additional loose photographs of travels depict the same period. One photograph album from 1904 and earlier includes family photographs, photographs of friends, and photographs of the Louisiana Purchase Exposition. Also found are numerous photographs of monuments and streetscapes from towns throughout France, taken by Storrs during the 1940s and 1950s. A small number of exhibition photographs depict an exhibition at the Museum of Beaugency, the Carnegie Institute, and other unidentified galleries. Also within this series is a notebook of photo negatives and the corresponding copy prints of the negatives. Original prints of most of these negatives are found in the three photograph albums mentioned above. Prints of the glass plate negatives are also found elsewhere in this series.
  Numerous photographs of artwork document Storrs' sculptural work as well as his paintings. Included are loose photographs arranged by subject as well as three albums and two portfolios of photographs of his work.
  This series has been partially scanned. Items not scanned include photographs of artwork, negatives, and glass plate negatives.
  Photographs are arranged by subject matter and format. Items are arranged chronologically within each folder. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and closed to researchers.
  - Photographs of John Storrs as a Child, circa 1885-1900 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Photographs of John Storrs as a Child, Duplicates and Negatives, circa 1885-1900; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Class Photographs, 1898-1904 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of John Storrs, circa 1901-1956; (4 folders; oversized items housed in Box 20) (Box 15, Folder 3-6)
  - Photographs of John Storrs, Duplicates and Negatives, circa 1901-1956; (2 folders; not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Photographs of John Storrs in Art School, circa 1912 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of John Storrs with Friends and Family, 1901-1948; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
  - Photographs of Marguerite Storrs, 1910-1955 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Storrs Family, Late 1800s-1917, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of Friends of John Storrs, circa 1905-1920s (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Photograph of Monique Storrs Booz with Marc Chagall and Others, 1950s (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Photographs of Maud Allan, 1905-1906 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Photographs of "Bernadette", circa 1910s; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of Arthur Bock, circa 1906 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of Gertrude Lambert, circa 1910 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Gertrude Lambert, Negatives, circa 1910; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Photographs of Studio Models, circa 1920s (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Photographs of John Storrs' Studio, circa 1909, 1933, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Photographs of Storrs Residences, circa early-1900s (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Photograph of Storrs Family Home, Chicago, circa late-1800s (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Photographs of Storrs Family Tombstones, Storrs, Ct., circa 1950s (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Photograph Albums (Box 15)
    - Album, circa 1904 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Album, circa 1905 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Album, circa 1906 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Album, circa 1907 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Photographs of Travels, circa 1906-1907; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 28-29)
  - Photographs of Travels, Negatives, circa 1906-1907; (Not scanned) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Photographs of Places (Box 15)
    - Beaugency, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Blois, France, 1944, 1953; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 32-33)
    - Chambord, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Chantecaille, France, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Chateau de Moulin, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Courbuson, France, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Fougeres, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Menou, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Mer, France, circa 1940s-1954; (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 40-41)
    - Muids, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Orleans, France, circa 1940-1954; (4 folders) (Box 15, Folder 43-46)
    - Romorantin, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Suvres, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Talcy, France, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Photograph of the Exterior of the Illinois State Capitol, circa late-1880s (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Exhibition Photographs, Museum of Beaugency, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Exhibition Photographs, Miscellaneous, 1938, circa 1973-1980 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Exhibition Photographs, Miscellaneous, circa 1970s (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Personal Photographs, circa late-1800s-1970 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Photographs of Artwork (Box 15)
    - "Rider with Bird" (Last work by Storrs), 1965 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Portrait Busts, circa 1920s-1940s; (3 folders) (Box 15, Folder 55-57)
    - Female Figures, circa 1930s-1960s; (4 folders) (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
    - Male Figures, 1909-1970s; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
    - Abstract Sculptures, circa 1920s-1970s; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
    - Horse Head Sculptures, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Sculptures Photographed by Arthur Siegel, circa 1960; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
    - Sculptures Photographed by Arthur Siegel, circa 1960 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Sculptures, circa 1930s-1960s; (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 12-14)
    - Paintings, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Artwork by Others, circa late-1800s (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Negatives, circa 1920s-1960s; (4 folders) (Box 16, Folder 17-20)
    - Album, circa 1910-1914 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Album, circa 1930; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
    - Album (Disbound), circa 1934; (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 24-26)
    - Portfolio of Photographs of Artwork, circa 1940s; (Oversized volume housed in Box 21) (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Portfolio of Photographs of Artwork, circa 1940s; (Oversized volume housed in Box 22) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Negative Notebook, circa 1905; (Not scanned) (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Copy Prints from Negative Notebook, circa 1905; (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
  - Copy Prints from Negative Notebook, circa 1905; (2 folders) (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Negatives from Negative Notebook, circa 1905; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 18, Folder 3-5)
  - Glass Plate Negatives, circa 1910s; 2 Glass negatives (Box MGP 1)
    Includes images of John Storrs.
  - Glass Plate Negatives, circa 1930s; 11 Glass negatives (Box MGP 2)
    Images include interior or studio and artwork.
  - Glass Plate Negatives, 1933; 5 Glass negatives (Box MGP 5)
    Includes images of Science Hall at the Century of Progress Exposition.
  - Glass Plate Negatives, circa 1930s; 14 Glass negatives (Box MGP 6)
    Includes images of artwork.
  - Oversize Photograph of John Storrs, circa 1930s; (Scanned with Box 15, F3-6) (Box 20)
  - Oversize Portfolio of Photographs of Artwork, circa 1940s; (See also Box 16, F27; not scanned) (Box 21)
  - Oversize Portfolio of Photographs of Artwork, circa 1940s; (See also Box 16, F28; not scanned) (Box 22)
- Artwork, 1895-1935; Series 8; 0.5 Linear feet Boxes 18, 20, OV 23